Suddenly Explorers! Suddenly Explorers!
This way! Fujita-ku sternust! This is Miyu Fujita from Ikinari Talk!
Please give me a call! This is the Ikinari Expedition!
This is Miyu Fujita, the captain of the expedition.
There is a reason for that.
Later today, Hinano-san and I are going to shoot a video of the expedition team.
I would like to ask Mr. Fujita to do a mission.
What is it?
Eat all the candy without the members knowing.
I've seen it before.
Have you seen it?
Mr. Yasumori took on this challenge before.
when he was taking a video.
without being noticed by the members next to him.
If you could eat all the candy I gave you without the members next to you knowing, you'd be cleared.
That's what I'd like to do with Hinano-san this time.
I'd like to have Fujitani-san do it against Hinano-san this time.
Are you confident?
Hinano-san has a good sense of humor, doesn't she?
Like an animal sense.
Yes, the sixth sense.
It's not climate.
That too.
Buber, it's like a strong feeling.
It's like a man's explanation, isn't it?
I'm not sure if it's a little too difficult for you, but I'm prepared to do it, even if it's almost the same as last time with Yasumori.
It's always been me first.
I'm the local favorite parent and child?
Umaibo Umaibo, Yasumori-san struggled with this one, and these pancakes, too.
It's got two of them in it, so... it won't make a sound, right?
I'm going to say, “Oooh!” Why? You're not good at this.
And a tough one.
Crackle Panic! If you clear this one, you'll get a little reward, so please work hard for it.
What's your enthusiasm for this one?
I'm representing Yamagata in the Eat candy without washing your hands.
I'm really hyped up and I'm going to beat Sakura Hinano, who has a great sense of femininity.
Let's do our best!
Today's member is Sakura Hinano. Today's member is Hinano Sakura. Pleased to meet you.
Hello, I'm Inari Explorers. Don't you have a partner today?
Fujitani-san and Hinano-san are going to shoot a video together later today.
But before that, there's a reason why I asked Hinano-san to come here alone.
The mission is to eat up all the candy without the members knowing.
without being noticed by the members!
I'm going to shoot a video with Fujitani-san, and if you can eat all the sweets I'm going to give to Hinano-san in the video without being recognized by Fujitani-san, you will get a reward.
Pancakes, gingo jelly, and these look good!
They're so good! I can't eat these in one bite, so it's pretty tough!
And the rest...
This is definitely going to be a sound! Crackle panic!
Miyu's favorite snack, Kalpas!
Well, it's easy to eat, because it's so tiny!
Well, keep some water on hand.
You can use it to cheat, water and all.
I'll put some more maiwa in the water.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
If he sees you like that, it's the end of the world.
What are you doing?
It's the end of the game when they find out.
So please do your best to finish the meal without being caught.
I think I can do it.
Are you confident?
A little.
The fact that it's Mr. Miu on the other end.
I don't think he'll notice, and even if he does, I don't think he'll say anything.
I'll just end up wondering what he's doing.
It's okay if they don't say anything.
If they don't say anything, that's okay too.
If they noticed and didn't say anything, that's a win.
Then, let's try to clear it up a little bit.
Do your best.
I'll do my best.
Mission in Candy is about to begin!
Start.
Inviel inviel time
No taketan No taketan
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, noNo, Tatakan. Then it was everyone.
No, it was everyone.
Please, I'm sorry, I know I'm going double-time here, but today's project is about the two of you.
Today's project was to come up with an original character for the Iinari Expedition.
That's right.
I think it's about time we had a mascot character for the expedition.
I'm looking forward to it.
Okay, I'd like to get started on the design, but... what's with the headdress, Mr. Fujitani?
I asked Fujitani to buy a pen.
She went to the store to buy pens, so I'm sure you can watch the video of her shopping trip.
There's a video clip of the shopping trip.
He bought a lot of things at that time, didn't he?
I'd like to go home now, and I'd like to ask you to design an original character for the expedition.
I'd like to go home... and design an original character for the Explorers Club.
I'm sure it's important, so please design a chair for us.
I'm sure there are some animals or something like that.
Or it could be totally fictitious!
You're right.
You can decide after you've written it.
Why not start with a name?
You're right.
Name is important.
A name that is easy to remember is good.
It's easy for the audience to remember.
If we're going to split it up between boys and girls...
Furitori can be the boy's name and Hinao the girl's.
Hinao can be the girl.
That Gombei Ohana pattern.
You want to do that? The Gombei flower pattern.
Okay.
Next to England.
Yes, sir.
That's good! Like Tan and Ken.
Tan and Ken? Tang and Ken.
Tan and Ken.
Put them together and you get Ken Tang.
You're acting like you don't want to design.
Design it. Design it, quickly.
Design it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. That's an educational program.
You're playing with it.
I'm watching from here.
I'm watching.
I'm watching it, I'm watching it, I'm watching it, I'm watching it, I'm watching it.
I'll write it down. I'll write it down, please. Kent? Takeshi, right?
No! KAN and KEN! KAN and KEN. Okay, KAN.
Okay, Ken.
Oh, are you okay? Are you alright? Alive and well.
Oh, my God, it's coming out so fast.
Be careful.
At times like that, you have to cover it up with a fork.
Yes.
I don't know...
I don't know.
Okay, okay.
I've decided.
I won't say.
It's not just what I think.
You can do whatever you want.
I see.
Concrete by Bruno Mars
TEMPLE
I've got a pretty good idea.
Really?
Yeah.
I'm working on it.
I think we should wear jerseys.
We're on an expedition.
That's true.
Once we're human...
You don't have to have a body. You don't have to have a body. It doesn't matter.
Really?
Worst case scenario, just the face.
I see.
Oh!
What? Suddenly?
No, I made a mistake.
You got an idea?
Okay. Salvation worked.
Really?
I don't know. Maybe I'll just get a jersey pink.
Because I'm a girl, right? Yeah.
I'm a girl.
But I'm gonna change the color tomorrow. Maybe something a little darker pink.
You know what?
Oh!
What is it? Do you make funny noises regularly?
Stop it, you're startling me.
Wait a minute, I made a mistake.
Why do I make so many mistakes?
I think I'll do it this way.
This one.
Wow.
One good binge.
Yeah, it's a good one.
It's a good bins.
Let's call him Bean Bean Bean Bean Bean Bean Bean Bean Bean Bean Bean Bean
Oh, I see.
Ken, right?
If you call it an expedition team, it's a good bingsu, isn't it?
That's right.
We shoot at the same place every time.
It's coming along nicely.
Norman Desk? This is like Tambali.
Tambali.
Tambali?
Yeah.Yeah. Yeah.
I see.
Yeah, it's Tan-chan.
It's going to look great when it's finished.
I'm so excited.
That much?
Here's my tip.
Yes, yes, yes.
Crackle, crackle, crackle.
Hmmm...
I wonder if you have any tips for me.
I see.
Like in tests.
Like on a Kanji test, I wonder if anyone around me has written anything.
That's not good.
Well, it's not good.
You've seen something like that, right?
Yes, there was.
Let's go look for it.
It's windy today.
It's windy.
It's windy. Let's go outside.
What's he doing?
I don't know.
It's a telescope, but you don't want to touch it.
What? What is it? He's squirming so much.
One more time, it's healing, and I think I'm gonna lose it.
Suddenly? Now? That's an experience.
Let me see.
Oh, my God, it's swollen.
It swells from time to time.
Swollen at the right time?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Ouch.
I'm confused about how your face looks.
I'm lost. I'm lost.
I'm so lost.
It's so hard to decide.
I think I'll go with this one.
What color should I choose?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I don't know.
It looks really good, but I...
Mari?
Hmm?
Is your dad's swelling up?
The left one...
Wasn't it the right one earlier?
The left one's growing back.
Now the left?
It's done!
Quick!
Ta-da!
This is Tan-chan.
Tanchan's “C” is for “Chan”.
I see.
Tanchan's “T” is for tambourine.
So cute!
This is a member.
Oh, wow! Really!
There's someone called Hikaru, isn't there?
Yes, he is.
It glows!
It really glows!
What a great idea!
I see... they're in the members' colors.
And they're wearing jerseys, too.
It reminds me of the Expedition. Reminds me of the expedition.
Isn't it amazing?
I've got a great character.
I know, right?
She says she loves you, Ken-kun.
So that's how it's set up.
He's her boyfriend.
By the way, he has nine lashes.
What?
So cute!
There are nine of them.
How did you do that in such a short time?
And the embarrassing cheek pout, is that nine lashes too?
No, not these.
Seven.
Ah, I did it.
You did it, Tanchan!
It's Tanchan, the tambourine.
That's great.
You did it?
Speaking of good vinci beans...
Ken-kun!
Katakana for “Ken”.
I love Tan-chan
First of all, I was particular about the shape of this bean.
It's simple.
Bean-like, isn't it?
The big head is also a key point.
The face is tiny, too.
They're all gathered in the middle.
Wearing a bow tie.
We're going to explore more and more.
Elephants.
Favorite food, elephant?
Elephant?
Food elephant. Food elephant
For example
Projects we've done so far
Like the Burikko Expedition.
I'll write it here.
It's going to be engraved?
Like a tattoo.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm getting more and more tattoos.
You're very physical.
Like a gold membership.
like a gold driver's license
One kind of black bean.
Can I have them side by side for a second?
Yes, ma'am.
It's a cute little tumbleweed.
Line 'em up.
And he's wearing a jersey.
He's a real explorer.
They're both long and wide.
Ken's not wearing any clothes.
Ken, put some clothes on.
Ken still doesn't have any fashion sense.
You're going to keep him at Ibeats?
That's right.
Three kittens for Tan.
Look, it says “Ken” in katakana.
That's right.
We've created a great character.
Yes, sir!
We're going on an expedition, Mr. Tan and Mr. Ken.
Thank you very much.
Yes, sir.
Mission accomplished!
Yay!
That's not what I meant.
What is it?
Please do the project we had a chance to do today. Please do the project you had a chance to do today.
Today's project is to create an original character, which is, of course, our real plan.
Let's eat all the candy without the members knowing!
It's for both of us.
What do you mean by this?
What do you mean by that?
I'm trying not to get caught.
And you're starting to eat something too!
I'm starting to think we're both in on the surprise.
I thought something was wrong.
I thought something was wrong, but we didn't notice and didn't tell each other.
You noticed, but you didn't say anything.
How did you feel about Hirono-san's mission today?
I can see it.
I saw the bag.
Something was stuck.
It's a mistake.
Yes, yes, yes.
You had your wisdom teeth in regularly.
I also noticed that you were eating them.
I was aware of it.
You mean you didn't tell us?
I thought it was strange.
I saw something, but I thought it was a woman.
I thought it was an illusion.
I didn't care. I was just going on my mission.
I thought, “Okay, I'll just finish one meal.
I was just trying to finish it.
You were doing it.
Yes.
This is the hard part.
We both felt it.
When did you notice?
Pretty much at the beginning.
Where did you notice it?
I'm pretty sure it was the “crackle, crackle, crackle” panic.
Yeah, so it was pretty much over. Yeah, so pretty much the end.
I think it's midway through.
I think I was more aware of it before that.
When did you notice it? Hinano's.
When did you see it? The bag.
What bag? Pancakes.
Is it the same gourmet?
I had some jelly tucked in here on my leg.
And I thought Miyu saw me.
Did she see me?
But I thought maybe she pretended not to notice.
I didn't see it.
I didn't notice.
And because I pretended not to notice...
What was that? I thought, “What?
And then he said something like...
And then he started talking like he was sure I was eating.
I'm sure he's eating.
With the mugging?
I thought it was a surprise.
He's so perceptive.
I thought he was saying that if Miyu had eaten it too.
I wondered if you were going to tell me.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
That's right.
We've been cheating on each other.
If we ate each other's food, we'd realize it.
We did.
I think I cheated in a lot of ways.
It's so good!
We ate for quite a while.
It's so simple.
You didn't say a word, you just ate.
That's strange, isn't it?
Yes.
It was unnatural.
He didn't talk at all.
He was moving too slowly. It's going too slow.
I've been eating a little bit.
Because, Ms. Fujita, look at this.
This sample right here.
Garbage!
You're trashing it?
Garbage.
Here's all the trash.
You put all the trash in the trash?
I shoved it in there.
I bought a bunch of candy bars that had nothing to do with that.
I bought a bunch of candy.
So we both completed the mission.
So we both knew.
We just didn't tell each other.
That's right.
No, we didn't.
I see.
We don't notice each other.
I don't notice.
The conclusion of today's showdown is...
A draw.
We both had good instincts, and we both cared.
That's it, isn't it?
Well, it was a fascinating battle.
Well, that concludes today's exploration.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.